{
    "subject": "Robin_Williams",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Mrs._Doubtfire",
    "human_readable": "Robin Williams created Mrs. Doubtfire.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9378849267959595,
            "question": "Was Robin Williams involved in writing the script for Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8798922896385193,
            "question": "Who created the character Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.624115526676178,
            "question": "Who played the role of Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5818005204200745,
            "question": "What year was Mrs. Doubtfire released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44513243436813354,
            "question": "Did Mrs. Doubtfire receive any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4144897758960724,
            "question": "Would you recommend watching Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.41081637144088745,
            "question": "What type of movie is Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39886802434921265,
            "question": "What is the main premise of the film Mrs. Doubtfire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28174394369125366,
            "question": "Is Robin Williams known for any other famous roles?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2691866457462311,
            "question": "What is the name of the character brought to life by Robin Williams?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Robin Williams created Mrs. Doubtfire.",
            "html": "yago_27951_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Robin Williams known for any other famous roles?",
            "html": "yago_27951_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the main premise of the film Mrs. Doubtfire?",
            "html": "yago_27951_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of movie is Mrs. Doubtfire?",
            "html": "yago_27951_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_159.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_175.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_195.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_27951_96.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents does not support the claim that Robin Williams created Mrs. Doubtfire. According to the text, Anne Fine wrote the novel \"Alias Madame Doubtfire\" which inspired the story of the movie Mrs. Doubtfire."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that the role of Mrs. Doubtfire was portrayed by Robin Williams, but they do not state that Robin Williams created the character. The character and the idea for Mrs. Doubtfire were based on a novel by Anne Fine, which provided the foundation for the movie's plot."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The Eyes on Cinema clip from 1993 shows Robin Williams talking about how he created the loving, Scottish voice for his character Euphegenia Doubtfire, but it does not imply that he \"created\" Mrs. Doubtfire as a person, rather than just portraying her in the film.",
            "category": 3
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Robin Williams did not create Mrs. Doubtfire; he portrayed the character of Peter Pan, who takes on the guise of the Scottish nanny Euphegenia Doubtfire as an act to remain a part of his children's lives after a messy divorce. The character and concept were created by Anne Fine in her novel \"Alias Madame Doubtfire,\" which served as the inspiration for the film.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}